{
    "id": "yexuqo",
    "name": "YeXuQo",
    "yomi": "エズコ",
    "text": [
        "音楽やグラフィックを作っています。ここ最近は、かわいらしいもの、小気味よいもの、涼しいものに惹かれるようになりました。",
        "I make music and graphics. I recently attracted to things that cute, comfortable and cool-looking."
    ],
    "link": [
        {
            "a": "SoundCloud",
            "href": "https://www.soundcloud.com/yexuqo/"
        },
        {
            "a": "Instagram",
            "href": "https://www.instagram.com/yexuqo/"
        }
    ],
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "Q1",
            "question": "Do you want to practice?",
            "jp": "練習したい？",
            "yes": "Yes i do",
            "left": "したい",
            "no": "No i don't",
            "right": "したくない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q2",
            "question": "Want a nice pen?",
            "jp": "いいペンがほしい？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "ほしい",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "いらない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q3",
            "question": "Have you ever had a fracture?",
            "jp": "骨折したことがある？",
            "yes": "Yes i have",
            "left": "ある",
            "no": "No i have never",
            "right": "ない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q4",
            "question": "Time",
            "jp": "時間は",
            "yes": "I want more!",
            "left": "もっとたくさんほしい",
            "no": "I would give it to someone",
            "right": "誰かにあげたい"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q5",
            "question": "Do you think a flower and a leaf is different?",
            "jp": "花と葉って違うと思う？",
            "yes": "it could be",
            "left": "違うかも",
            "no": "it might be the same",
            "right": "同じかも"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q6",
            "question": "What is the difference between the daytime and the night?",
            "jp": "昼と夜の差は？",
            "yes": "brightness",
            "left": "明るさ",
            "no": "temperature",
            "right": "温度"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q7",
            "question": "Can you imagine the inside of the soil where cactus is planted?",
            "jp": "サボテンの土の中を想像できる？",
            "yes": "Yes i can",
            "left": "できる",
            "no": "No i can't",
            "right": "できない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q8",
            "question": "Do you have any exciting event next year?",
            "jp": "来年の楽しみがある？",
            "yes": "Yes!",
            "left": "ある",
            "no": "No...",
            "right": "ない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q9",
            "question": "Are you happy if you know?",
            "jp": "知れたらうれしい？",
            "yes": "Yes i think so",
            "left": "そう思う",
            "no": "No i don't think so",
            "right": "そうは思わない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q10",
            "question": "Ended up as you want?",
            "jp": "思い通りになった？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "なった",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "ならなかった"
        }
    ]
}